<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Jorge Ávila</title>
    <link>https://www.uv.es/jorpago/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://www.uv.es/jorpago/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.uv.es/jorpago/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.uv.es/jorpago/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.uv.es/jorpago/project/advent-of-code-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.uv.es/jorpago/project/advent-of-code-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://adventofcode.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Advent of Code&lt;/a&gt; is an Advent calendar of small programming puzzles for a variety of skill sets and skill levels that can be solved in any programming language you like. People use them as a speed contest, interview prep, company training, university coursework, practice problems, or to challenge each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been using them to improve my coding experience and my knowledge in algorithms. I have participated in the 2017 and 2018 editions completing all the problems. Here I present my solutions for the year 2017, I have tried to develop clear python scripts that lead to the solutions in a efficient and easy way (almost always :D). I am trying to create useful contents related with the problems, for example the featured image in this post is the day 14 solution visualization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really anxious for the 2019 edition and I am planning to create jupyter notebooks for the solution of each day, explaining clearly the code and working on the visualization or interesting stuff related with each problem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
